Friendship has its benefits.
No Strings Attached is a comedy, romance film directed by Ivan Reitman.
Emma is a busy doctor who sets up a seemingly perfect arrangement when she offers her
best friend Adam a relationship with one rule: No strings attached.
But when a fling becomes a thing, can sex friends stay best friends?
Emma Kurtzman, played by Natalie Portman.
Adam Franklin, played by Ashton Kutcher.
Alvin Franklin, played by Kevin Kline.
Dr. Stephen Metzner, played by Cary Elwes.
Patrice, played by Greta Gerwig.
Lucy, played by Lake Bell.
No Strings Attached is a 2011 American romantic comedy film
directed and co-produced by Ivan Reitman.
Starring Natalie Portman and Ashton Kutcher, the film is about two friends who decide to make a pact
to have a "no strings attached" relationship, without falling in love with each other.
The film was released in the United States on January 21, 2011, to mixed reviews, with praise for the
lead pair's performances and chemistry, but criticism for its direction and screenplay.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship, casual
meeting, sexual humor, student of medicine, friends.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.